nealschaffer.com 2012-05-07

# Privacy Policy

**PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT**

Your privacy is important to Windmills Marketing.  This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that Windmills Marketing collects, and the ways in which Windmills Marketing uses that personal information.

 **This privacy policy statement**

This statement is based on a [free privacy policy](http://www.freenetlaw.com/free-privacy-statement.html) form made available by contract experts SEQ Legal.  SEQ Legal supplies a wide range of commercial legal documents, including [novation agreement ](http://www.template-contracts.co.uk/acatalog/novation_agreements.html)templates.

 **Personal information collection**

Windmills Marketing may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:

  * [information about your use of this website (including [INSERT DETAILS]);]
  * [information that you provide using for the purpose of registering with the website (including [INSERT DETAILS]);]
  * [information about transactions carried out over this website (including [INSERT DETAILS]);]
  * [information that you provide for the purpose of subscribing to the website services (including [INSERT DETAILS]); and]
  * [any other information that you send to [NAME].]

 **Using personal information**

Windmills Marketing may use your personal information to:

  * administer this website;
  * personalize the website for you;
  * enable your access to and use of the website services;
  * publish information about you on the website;
  * send to you products that you purchase;
  * supply to you services that you purchase;
  * send you statements and invoices;
  * collect payments from you; and
  * send you marketing communications.

Where Windmills Marketing discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement.

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, Windmills Marketing may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.

 **Securing your data**

Windmills Marketing will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

 **Cross-border data transfers**

Information that Windmills Marketing collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which Windmills Marketing operates to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the internet and may be available around the world.

You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information.

 **Updating this statement**

Windmills Marketing may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website.

You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.

 **Other websites**

This website contains links to other websites.

Windmills Marketing is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.

 **Contact Windmills Marketing**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or Windmills Marketing’s treatment of your personal information, please write to:

  * by email to neal at windmillnetworking dot com; or
  * by post to 1280 Bison Ave., B9-373, Newport Beach, CA 92660 USA

Windmills Marketing, 14271 Jeffrey Rd., Suite 177, Irvine, CA 92620 | (888) 541-3429 | info@windmillnetworking.com
